<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Abigail Elizabeth</title>
    <link>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Abigail Elizabeth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 20:45:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Thing About Soulmates</title>
      <link>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/soulmates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 20:45:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/soulmates/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a lot of thinking about the whole concept of &amp;ldquo;soulmates&amp;rdquo; and it seems a bit far-fetched. Can a person really have one person out of the billions of people on Earth that is to be their perfect match? If so, the odds of finding a soulmate are remarkably low. So I think that a soulmate is just the person God meant for you to be with. Or for you non-religious folks, a soulmate is the best possible fit for you given where you go in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One More Hug</title>
      <link>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/onemorehug/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 21:39:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/onemorehug/</guid>
      <description>My boyfriend and I do this thing I call One More Hug, and it&amp;rsquo;s one of my favorite things about our relationship.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure which of us started it, but I remember vividly when we were on a date as I hugged him goodbye, it was so hard to say goodbye. I walked away to my car sadly and put on my seatbelt and heard a tapping at the passenger window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braveheart</title>
      <link>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/braveheart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 20:19:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/braveheart/</guid>
      <description>Okay guys, so I watched the movie Braveheart a night or two ago, and I&amp;rsquo;m a wee bit angry at this thing they call a &amp;lsquo;movie&amp;rsquo;. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched it, I highly DO NOT recommend, because it is sad and angering. But for those of you who haven&amp;rsquo;t watched it, there are basically 8 steps to the plot.
 There&amp;rsquo;s a dude named William Wallace. He likes a girl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dreaded AP Biology Test</title>
      <link>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/apbio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 17:51:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/apbio/</guid>
      <description>The day had finally come. I was testing by myself, with a beady-eyed old lady who looked like she could easily cut off my hands. She pointed at my chair, and I sat down promptly, and began to remember all the things I did, or perhaps didn&amp;rsquo;t do to prepare for the Advanced Placement Biology Exam.
I remembered the girl with the long brown hair and the girl with the obnoxiously red hair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/myfirstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 22:00:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stereotypicalnerd.com/posts/myfirstpost/</guid>
      <description> At this point, I am currently testing my ability to post to my website. This is test one.
-Abbie Over and out
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>